嘿 伙计们 马修和莉莉人呢
Hey, guys.Where are Marshall and Lily?
发生了一些很糟糕的事儿
Something terrible happened.
他们俩怎么了 他们是在医院么
Are they okay?Are they in the hospital?
不
No.
发生了一些比这个糟糕多了的事儿
Somewhere much... much worse.
长岛
Long Island!
今晚 我们就要永远搬去长岛了
Tonight, we're moving out there for good.
哦耶 这是我们新居的备用钥匙
Yeah. Here are your spare keys to our new house.
长岛
Long Island?
我不理解
I don't understand.
你们在这儿也能买到皮肤晒黑喷雾啊
You can get spray tans here.
我从来都不敢相信
I never let myself
会真有这么一天
believe this day would really come.
就好像是 那次我们去看五口之家
It's like when they canceled
他们放了两次鸽子
Party of Five for the second time.
我的意思是他们还顺带取消了户外运动
I mean when they...canceled sports.
亲们 我们还是可以经常见面的啊
Guys, we'll still see each other all the time,
而且我们可以煲电话粥啊
and we'll talk on the phone.
再者 即使人们都说有了孩子
And I know people say that having kids means
就等于和你的朋友们永别了 但是...
you won't see your friends anymore, but...
哦 老天爷 这就是我们的永别了是么
Oh, God, this is good-bye, isn't it?
别 别这样
No. Stop it.
亲们 这不会
Guys, this doesn't
改变任何事情的
change anything.
我们只隔了46分钟的火车程而已
We are only a 46-minute train ride away.
只要有空
Just pop out
你们可以随时来找我们啊
whenever you want.
这么说 我可以坐这儿咯
So... I guess this seat is open.
我还是去拿个椅子吧
I'll go get a chair.
好吧 就这样了么
So that's it.
不再有马修了
No more Marshall.
不再有莉莉了
No more Lily.
他们都不在了
They're gone.
这就意味着
Which means...
我们中再也没有那对无聊的
no lame married couple
总是把我的奇思妙想扼杀在摇篮中的小夫妻了
shooting down all my amazing ideas.
伙计们 好消息
Guys, great news.
哥是新一届领导人啦
I'm the new leader of the gang!
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十四集
翻译:  47.4 邵小庚 Roy 安达小充 小草莓 Cathy
后期+统筹: Cathy  校对: 47.4 Andie 园丁姐姐
巴尼是小团体的新头头啦
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
马修和莉莉差不多把新居都装点好了
Marshall and Lily were almost done decorating their new home.
-看上去感觉好多了   -是啊
-I like it there much better.   -Yeah.
不过还有一个问题
There was only one problem.
不对
Wrong!
这个不该这么放
This can't go here.
孩子们 当那个原本和莉莉很疏远的父亲
Kids, when he found out she was pregnant,
发现女儿怀孕了
Lily's estranged father
出人意料地出现在了他女儿的门前
unexpectedly showed up on her doorstep.
这种姿态让莉莉很欣慰
It was a gesture she appreciated.
但是两个礼拜后 莉莉和马修已经受够了
But after two weeks,they'd had just about enough.
这个应该放在这儿
That has to go there
来盖住这些开裂的地板
to cover up the splintery floorboard.
而且你们也不该
And you can't hang
把这个照片挂在这儿
this picture here.
这个墙上不是石膏 而是干的牙膏 挂不住的
This isn't plaster;it's dried toothpaste.
伙计们 你们真该为我在这儿而高兴
Guys, you're so lucky I'm here.
我就在这屋子里长大
I grew up in this house.
我对这房子了如指掌
I know it like the back of my hand.
而且这落地灯也绝对不该竖在这儿
And this lamp absolutely cannot be here.
为什么
Why not?
会挡住我看那个小寡妇罗德里格斯
Blocks my view of the Widow Rodriguez
做那些有氧运动的视线的
doing her Jane Fonda workouts.
你不觉得她有点老了么 爸
Isn't she a little old, Dad?
哦 你没赶着见到她年轻那会儿
Oh, you didn't see her when I was a kid.
在我的脑海里 她永远是54岁
In my mind, she'll always be 54.
我能理解他的本意是好的 但是我受不鸟了
I know he means well, but I can't take it anymore.
他不会离开的 而且
He won't leave,and-and he's acting
而且就感觉他成了这房子的主人一样
like this is his house.
我懂
No, I know.
他还总是给我留这些烦人的纸条
And these annoying notes he keeps leaving around?
在我打鼓的时候需要绝对的安静
"I need absolute silence when practicing the drums."
别碰那些我放在床头柜里的时尚杂志
"Do not touch the fudge in my nightstand."
我们需要在床头柜里弄一些蚂蚁陷阱
"We need ant traps for my nightstand."
我发现我只能藏在这个房间里
I find myself hiding out here
因为这里是唯一一个
just because it's the only room in the house
他无法对我们指手画脚的地方
where he can't boss us around.
好消息
Great news.
我在这些旧的对讲机里装了些新电池
I put new batteries in the old intercom system.
现在我们可以随时的交谈了
Now we can communicate at all times.
完毕
Mickey out.
看看我们的专座都变成什么样子了
Look at what's become of our booth.
就好像我的那个技校老师的手一样
Looks like my old shop teacher's hand--
少了点什么
just sort of missing something.
够了
Enough!
我受够你们俩怨天尤人
I am sick of you two wallowing in sadness,
而不去做一些积极向上的事儿
instead of doing the healthy thing
并假装那些离开你的人
and pretending anyone who leaves you
从来就不存在
never existed in the first place.
我不想同意巴尼说的
I hate to agree with Barney's
这些脑残且应该被忽视的话
near-paralyzing abandonment issues,
但是他说到点子上了
but he has a point.
你们不能因为两个好朋友搬走了
You can't just stop living
就让生活停滞不前
because two of your friends moved away.
就是这样
Precisely.
现在 作为这个团体的新一届领导人
Now, as new group leader,
我提议我们该去做点
I say we go out and do something
以前他们俩在的时候 我们永远做不了的事儿
that we never would have done with Marshall and Lily here.
哦
Ooh.
还记得我某年某月某日
Remember that amazing idea
提出的那个绝妙的想法么
I had that one time?
-我们去脱衣舞俱乐部吧   -没门儿
-Let's go to a strip club.   -Nope.
你们意下如何
So what do you say?
来宣告光溜溜的独立吧
Let's declare our independence
来个光妞妞的舞怎么样
with an on-da-peen dance.
光光的妞的大腿舞
On-the-peen dance.
行行 我们听见了
No, we got it. We got it.
咱去脱衣舞俱乐部吧
Let's go to a strip club!
额
Well...
不管去哪我都想他们
I'm going to miss them anywhere.
借酒浇愁也没用
Might as well see some cans while I'm at it.
这事交给我
I'll take it!
罗宾 凯文 你俩来不
Robin, Kevin, you in?
孩子们 在刚开始谈恋爱的时候
Kids, early in any relationship,
有这么一个阶段 你不能拒绝任何事
there's a phase where you don't say no to anything.
因为你想让人觉得你有趣
Because you want to seem interesting...
爱冒险
adventurous...
以及灰常开放
and open-minded.
我管这叫恋爱早期胆怯症
I call it Early Relationship Chicken.
唔 姐开放得很
Well, I'm open to anything.
噢 我也是嘿
Oh, mos' def.
-那   -那
-So...   -So...
我可不想去脱衣舞俱乐部
I don't want to go to a strip club.
我真心不想去脱衣舞俱乐部
但我也不想让他觉得我太古板了
But I don't want him to think I'm some prude.
我去 咱俩已经 那 了好一会了
Man, we've been saying "So" For a while.
-好啊  -好啊
-Yeah!  -Yeah!
赞
Yes!
今夜将成为传...
Tonight is going to be legen--
等下 去看脱衣舞不太妥当吧
Wait, are we sure it's a good idea to go to a strip club?
闭嘴吧 莉莉 现在是我做主...奇
Shut up, Lily! I'm in charge now-- dary!
手机没信号
I've got no cell reception.
我想给泰德打电话
I wanted to call Ted.
我感觉太别扭了
This feels weird.
上回我离他这么远
The last time I lived this far from him
还是在我做交流生的时候
was my semester abroad.
你没做过交流生啊
You never did a semester abroad.
我们住在学校的两头那会儿
That's what I called it when we lived
就是这么叫的
on opposite sides of campus.
不行
Wrong!
别告诉你是要插这个插座吧
Please tell me you're not plugging that in there.
没错 米奇 我正这么打算来着
Yes, Mickey, that's exactly what I'm doing.
成 成 我啥也不说了
All right, fine. I won't say anything.
只不过 我从小
It's... just that this was my room
就在这屋里长大
when I growing up,
比你多知道那么一点点
so I know it a little better than you.
这里好多美好回忆啊
Lot of great memories here.
尤其是发现了自己身体的那些奥秘
Mostly just discovering my body.
够了够了
That's it.
米奇 自从你来了
Mickey, since you got here,
你就摆出一副固执己见和评判他人的嘴脸
you've been nothing but judgmental and pushy
而且恶心地沉迷在你的青少年性生活里
and strangely obsessed with your adolescent sex life.
明天早上
Tomorrow morning,
你赶紧搬出去
you're out of here.
额 我 我只是想帮你们
Well, I-I've just been trying to help you...
我们不需要
We don't need your help!
我
I...
噢 没关系 亲爱的
Oh, it-it's okay, baby.
迟早得这样
It had to be done.
哎呀 好悲桑啊
Too bad the one person
本来有一个人能阻止你搞出这些意外的
who could stop you from making mistakes like that
可惜他下个月就要被赶走了哦 亲
was told he has to move out next month.
-明天   -明天
-Tomorrow!   -Tomorrow!
要不要给你们跳个舞啊
Would either of you like a dance?
我早就准备好了
I'm always ready to rock.
时刻准备着
And I'm always ready to roll.
-那   -那
-So...   -So...
我可不想要大腿舞
I'm not ready to rock.
我会把持不住的
Rolling makes me dizzy.
-好啊   -好啊
-Hell, yeah!   -Yeah!
我要请客给我男朋友一个大腿舞
I'm buying my man a lap dance,
因为这就才是我的风格
'cause that's just how I do!
嗨起来吧
Party like a rock star!
摇...滚...夜...
Party like a rock star...
呀哈 伙计们
Uh, hey, guys.
我是泰德
It's Ted.
额 你们搬家搬得挺忙吧
Um... you're probably busy with the move still.
额
Um...
想扯淡的时候 打给我啊
Give me a call if you want to gab.
扯淡这词用的不大好
Sorry about using the word "Gab."
泰德 你就别为马修和莉莉憔悴了
Ted, stop pining over Marshall and Lily.
给自己留点尊严成不
Have some self-respect.
喏 把这五块钱叼嘴里
Now, put this fiver in your mouth so...
然后那个长一双勾魂眼的舞娘
that stripper with the lazy eye
就会走过把钱拿走
can vacuum it up with...
-巴尼   -啥
-Barney!   -Wh-what?
想他们不犯法 好不
I'm allowed to miss them, okay?
他们是我最好的两个朋友
They're my two best friends.
我才是你最好的两个朋友
I'm your two best friends!
咱今天来这里
And we're here tonight
就是要证明你根本不用想谁
to show you there's no need to miss something
因为你有更好更棒的哦
when you can replace it with something better.
先生们 有请 茉莉！
Gentlemen, say hello to J-J-J-Jasmine!
还记得她不
Remember her?
之前 我们发现
- So, a while back, we discovered-
莉莉有个复刻版
Lily had a doppelganger
是个俄罗斯脱衣舞娘
who was a Russian stripper.
看看她吧 泰德
Look at her, Ted.
她看起来就像
She's just like old,
人老珠黄的莉莉
less-good Lily,
但是绝妙的是 她从不发号施令
but instead of bossing us around,
她袒胸露乳
she shows us her boobs.
手拿开
No touching.
额好吧 还是有一点点管东管西
Okay, a little bossing us around.
我叫她升级版莉莉哟
I call her Better Lily.
嘿 升级版莉莉 给我的朋友来段大腿舞吧
Hey, Better Lily, please dance for my friend.
巴尼 我真的不需要大腿舞
Barney, I don't need a lap dance.
我得和我的朋友谈谈
I need to talk to my friends.
谁说你不能双线操作的
Who says you can't do both?
和她唠唠嗑 她又不是没长耳朵
Talk to her. She's got ears.
对 她确实听着呢
Yes, she does have ears.
你想摸我的小妞的咪咪吗
You want to touch my girlfriend's boobs?
50刀
50 bucks.
等下 升级版莉莉正和这头兽人交往么
Wait-- Better Lily is dating this behemoth?
像不像你们认识的一个人
Sound like anyone you know?
这是升级版马修
That's New Marshall.
新的五人帮达成了
This is our gang now.
喂 筒子们 还是我
Hey, guys, Ted again.
有点感觉你们忘了我了
Starting to think you forgot about me.
或者哪个酷酷的邻居替换了我
Or replaced me with some cool neighbor.
他是谁
What's his name?!
开玩笑的
I'm totally kidding.
无论如何 呃
Anyway, uh...
我就是想尽力记住你长啥样而已
just trying to remember what your faces look like.
泰德 当你在一个能有酒喝的脱衣舞俱乐部时
Ted, when they serve alcohol at a strip club,
就不该表现得这么娘娘腔
you're not allowed to show your vagina.
给哥100刀 你就无所不见了 我的朋友
100 bucks, and you will see the world, my friend.
他们居然不接我电话
They're already ignoring my calls?
看 我是很现实的
Look, I'm realistic.
我知道我必须得习惯一个人去看牙医
I knew I'd have to get used to going to the dentist alone,
但我不认为他们就真的完全和我绝交了
but I didn't think they'd cut me out completely.
要是他们无情
If they don't
休怪我们不义
need us, we don't need them.
好样的 你终于看开了
Yes! Finally!
附带一句 你知道她怎么开的酒瓶子吗
By the way, did you see how she opened that bottle?
嗷
Whoa.
在郊区停电真的 真的好黑啊
Lights out in the suburbs is... is really dark.
保险丝盒在哪里
Where's the fuse box?
不晓得
I don't know.
我知道它在哪里哟
I know where it is.
如果我不是忙着打包行李的话
Maybe I could fix it for you,
或许我可以帮你们修好它哦
if I wasn't so busy packing.
你知道么
You know what?
我敢说这保险丝盒子在地下室
I bet the fuse box is in the basement.
我就 我就自己找到它
I'll just... I'll go find it myself.
这能有多纠结
How hard can it be?
就像你刚刚撞到桌子角一样纠结哟
As hard as that desk you just walked into?
干得好 米奇
Good burn, Mickey.
该奖励你一颗床头柜里的小软糖
You deserve a little nightstand fudge for that one.
我眼睛该看哪儿啊
Where do I look?
我可不能盯着她胸部
I mean, I can't look at her chest.
我勒个擦 瞄到了
Damn it! I just did.
希望罗宾没注意到
Maybe Robin didn't notice.
哟呵 他还真喜欢那对球啊
Man, he's really up in those jugs.
狠狠地摇啊 宝贝
Shake it, baby!
要玩就玩个痛快
A playa's gotta play!
怪怪的
This is weird.
我就看着她的眼睛好了
I'll just look her in the eyes.
他是不是爱上这个脱衣舞娘了啊
Is he falling in love with this stripper?
赶紧干点儿看上去正常的事儿吧
Quick, do something cool.
干的漂亮 小伙子
Make it rain, son!
钱算个鸟
Money ain't no thang!
我去 里面有一张二十刀啊
Damn it, there was a 20 in there.
你好啊 埃瑞克森先生
Hello, Mr. Eriksen.
从风铃声里我听出来
From the sound of the wind chimes,
你已经成功抵达一楼了
I hear you've made it to the first floor.
行 我告诉你 米奇
Okay... you know what, Mickey?
你那些糟糕的游戏套路可以省省了
You can save the creepy game master routine.
我只是有一丢丢的害怕而已
It's only kind of terrifying me.
喔 游戏才刚刚开始而已
Oh, but the game has just begun.
它的名字是 在去地窖换保险丝的路上
I call it "Try Not to Bang into All the Furniture and Stuff
不要碰到那些家具什么的哦 小马修
on Your Way to the Fuse Box in the Basement, Marshall."
这只是个暂定名称哟
That's just a working title.
嘿
Hey!
你眉毛沾了些脱衣舞娘胸口的荧粉哦 老皮条客
Got a little boob glitter on your eyebrow, Mac Daddy.
这是我的本职工作啦
Straight pimpin'.
巴尼 你也沾到了一点哦
Barney, you got a little bit, too.
哪儿
Where?
我弄掉了吗
Did I get it?
嗯 你弄掉了
Yeah, you got it.
谁需要马修和莉莉啊
Who needs Marshall and Lily?
我们是新的五人帮
We got a new gang,
而且我们要在一起出去玩
and we're all going to hang out together forever.
我要换班了
My shift is done.
拜拜
Good-bye.
等下 停一停
Wait, stop!
严格意义上说 这首歌没完
Technically, this song's not over,
所以你还是我们的
so we still own you.
而且我们是挚友啊
Plus we're best friends!
下一站去哪儿
Where to next?
我们去地下赌场
We go to underground poker game
那里是个快废弃的疯人院
in mostly-abandoned insane asylum.
好
Yes!
这会超级赞的
This is gonna be awesome,
另外 我要你们全都记住
and when it is, I want you all to remember
是谁带你们去那儿的 是巴尼?斯丁森
who led you there: Barney Stinson,
新的老大
new group leader.
耶
Yay!
这些筹码都是哥的了
I'm winning all your chippies!
别喝了
Let's not drink when we're...
我口渴 没事的
I'm thirsty; it's good.
没事的
It's good.
马修 我刚刚想起来
Marshall, I just remembered
我之前看到垃圾桶旁边的抽屉里有盒火柴
I saw a box of matches in the drawer by the trash can.
哦 谢了 宝贝
Okay, thanks, baby.
莉莉 我找不到啊
Lily, I can't find them.
你在找这个吗
Looking for these?
哦 对了 你看不见我
Oh, right, you can't see me.
我正在烧掉你极度渴望的火柴
Um, well, I'm burning the matches you so desperately need.
啊 噢 喔哦
Aah, ooh, ow!
喔哦
Ow.
哈哈哈
Hah! Oh!
米奇 你猜是谁找到了地下室的楼梯
Mickey... guess who found the basement stairs?
用不了多久我就能到达保险盒那里
I'll be down at that fuse box in no time,
而当我到达那里
and when I get there,
我保证我会弄清保险盒是怎么工作的
I'm sure that I'll figure out how fuse boxes work,
然后修好它
so it'll be fine.
嘿 马修
Hey, Marshall,
我知道我一直在唬你
I know I've been messing with you,
但说真的 第二个台阶 不要
but seriously, that second step, don't...
我不想听 米奇
I don't want to hear it, Mickey.
哦 我的膝盖
Oh, my knee!
喔哦
Ow!
小心我的架子鼓
And watch out for my drum set.
我又赢了
I win again!
我是虚张声势的
I was bluffing.
我甚至牌数都不够
I didn't even have enough cards.
泰德 别再赢了
Ted, please stop winning.
嘿 看啊 这就是纽约的摩天大楼
Hey, look, it's the New York City skyline.
我们建了 一座筹码之城
We built Chip City
哼 哈
Uh, uh!
我们用你们的钱建了一座筹码之城
We built Chip City on all your dough
建了一座筹码之城 一起唱
? Built Chip City Hit it!
你知道吗 蝴蝶刀
You know Butterfly-knife.
我想到纹身脸可能会这么做
I'd expect this from Face Tattoo...
或者刀疤脸
or Cheek Scar,
或者拉瑞
or Larry,
但你不行
but not you.
为什么我没有绰号
Why don't I get nickname?
因为你有太多特点了 拉瑞
Because you have too many things, Larry.
绰号只能根据一点取
You get one thing!
看到了吗 这就是为什么你要带着新马修
See, that's why you bring New Marshall.
我们要去屠宰场的派对
We go to party in slaughterhouse.
你们来吗
You come?
求你了 上帝 不要啊
Please, God, no.
别再让我领导这个小团体了
Don't let me be in charge of the gang anymore.
我无法相信凯文大夫在三年前
I can't believe Dr. Kevin doesn't remember me
的治疗之后居然不记得我
from our sessions three years ago.
他是那个刺伤
Is that the lunatic
所有狱警的疯子吗
that stabbed all those prison guards?
我们一定要去那个派对
We gotta hit that party!
我永远都找不到真爱了
I'll never find love.
我们一定要去那个派对
We got to hit that party!
好极了
Sweet.
莉莉
Lily?
我想我们搬到郊外就是个错误
I think we made a mistake moving out to the suburbs.
我想念我们的家了
I miss our home.
我想念我们和朋友们的小雅座了
I miss our booth with our friends.
而且我很确定有一根鼓棒插在了
And I'm pretty sure I have a drumstick...
某个非常不好的地方
somewhere bad.
爸爸 你为什么要这么做
Dad, why are you acting like this?
嗯 我本来只是想帮忙的
Well, I was just trying to be helpful,
但你们却希望我在七月四独立日之前搬走
but you guys want me out by the Fourth of July.
是明天
Tomorrow.
你知道一个有用的爸爸
You know what a helpful father,
更不要说一个爷爷会怎么做吗
not to mention grandfather, might do?
把灯打开
Get these lights back on.
好了 马修 听好了
Okay, Marshall, listen up.
我会把你指引到保险盒那里
I'm gonna get you to that fuse box.
你不能直接下来帮我做吗
Can't you just come down here and do it for me, please?
我对这所房子一无所知
I don't know anything about this house.
不 马修
No, Marshall...
你对你的房子一无所知
you don't know anything about your house.
好了 我们有很多工作要做
All right, we got a lot of work to do.
在这等着 我们把你
Wait here, we get you
弄到派对的VPI名单上去
on VPI list for party.
你给我们 呃 每人200美元
You give us, uh, $200 per person.
服务费
Cover charge.
服务费也太高了吧
That's pretty steep for a cover charge.
这可是非常好的派对
Is very good party.
是纽约扬基和可口可乐的派对
Is party for, uh, New York "Yunkees" And Coca-Cola.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
可口可乐扬基派对
A Coca-Cola Yankees party?
听上去不像骗人的
That sounds like a real thing.
好了 现在 马修 向前走三步
Okay, now, Marshall, take three steps forward,
同时俯身躲避天花板上坏了的风扇
while ducking underneath the broken ceiling fan.
现在面向你的左面
Now look to your left
吐口水
and spit.
那是加热器
That's the water heater.
离它远点
Want to stay away from that.
那个小宝贝可比穿着紧身衣的
That baby is hotter than
罗德里格斯家的寡妇还要火热
the Widow Rodriguez in a unitard.
好了 现在 通过洗衣机和烘干机
Okay, now past the washer and dryer
是最难的部分了
is the hardest part.
你必须从乒乓球桌下面匍匐爬过去
You're gonna have to belly-crawl underneath the ping-pong table
小心不要碰到它
and don't so much as nudge it.
为什么不能碰
Why not?
因为有900快多米诺骨牌摆成了
Because there are 900 dominos set up
芭芭拉 伊登的形状
in the shape of Barbara Eden.
我是太空仙女恋的超级超级粉丝
Big, big I Dream Of Jeannie fan.
完成了
I'm clear.
我不知道这是什么声音 米奇
I don't know what that sound is, Mickey.
那是芭芭拉 伊登永远不会和我上床的声音
That's the sound of Barbara Eden never banging me.
这就是那个声音
That's what that is.
爸爸 把它打开
Dad, get it back.
求你了
Come on.
好吧 马修
Okay, Marshall,
往前三步
take three steps forward,
你就到了保险盒
and you should be at the fuse box.
你觉得他成功了么
Do you think he made it?
我做到了
I did it!
不 马修
No, Marshall...
你们做到了
you did it.
有意思的是 受那个晚上的启发
fun fact,that night inspired
米奇开发了唯一一款成功的桌游
Mickey's one and only successful board game--
这里有破裂的地板与生锈的铁钉
With splintery floorboards and rusty nails
小心别被刺穿
? Make sure you don't get impaled ?
停电大冒险
? Lites Out!
奥德林游戏出品
Brought to you by Aldrin Games!
恩 从那个妓女服务过的对象
Well, judging from how many clients
的数量来看
that hooker has serviced,
我想说我们来这已经快一个小时了
I'd say we've been here almost an hour.
泰德 我们被抢劫了
Ted, we've been robbed.
升级版莉莉和新版马修不可能打劫我们
Better Lily and New Marshall would never rob us.
他俩是我们最好的朋友
They're our best friends.
大家淡定 哥待会要去打劫这些二货们
该死 泰德
Damn it, Ted.
新版马修是一只动物园跑路熊
New Marshall is an escaped zoo bear
那个升级版莉莉唯一的优点 就是比莉莉
and the only thing that Better Lily is better at than our Lily
的手工活更好些（邪恶的小巴..）
is over-the-pants hand stuff.
哥猜的
I'm assuming.
哥得承认
I'll admit it.
哥不能继续领导这个组了
I can't lead this group.
我们需要马修和莉莉
We need Marshall and Lily.
他们不是走了么
But they're gone, aren't they?
我的意思是 一开始是一周小聚几次
I mean, it'll go from seeing them a couple times a week,
然后一月小聚几次
to a couple times a month,
最后就只有假期派对才能见面了
and then it'll just be holiday parties.
时过境迁
Then the years pass,
然后你发现马修已经翘辫子了
and you find out Marshall's dead,
然后你起初只是作为莉莉的情感寄托
and you're there for Lily emotionally at first,
却发展成肉体关系 然后你产生了内疚感
but then it becomes sexual, and you feel guilty,
不过有可能那会让这段关系变得更淫荡和美妙
but maybe that guilt just makes it dirtier and better...
不 我不会让那发生的
No, I won't let that happen.
特别是最后那部分
Especially that last part.
听着 我知道我今夜是有点小醉和天真
Look, I know I've been a little drunk and naive tonight,
不过接下来要听我的
but here's what's gonna happen.
首先 我们留下一张纸条
First, we're gonna leave a note
给升级版莉莉和大块头 以防他们担心
for Better Lily and Arvydas, they're worriers.
然后
Oh, buddy. Then,
我们去拜访仅此一家的马修和别无分店的莉莉
we're gonna go see Only Marshall and One-Of-A-Kind Lily
因为他们是我们最好的朋友
because they're our best friends
而且我们离他们只有四十六分钟的路程
and they're only 46 minutes away.
你们同意么
Are you with me?
哥有点嫉妒你掌权 不过可行 我们走吧
Kind of resent the power grab, but okay, let's go!
嘿
Hey,
你想跟我们一起去长岛么
do you want to come to Long Island with us?
呃 那个 离天亮还有几个小时呢
Uh, well, still a few more hours before the sun comes up.
所以呢
So...
-不 -不?
No. No?
有那么糟糕么
Is that bad?
不 这样很好
No, it's great.
噢 那感觉太棒了
Ooh, that felt so good.
我是个标准死宅
I hate doing things and going anywhere!
这些经历太糟糕了
Oh, new experiences suck!
既然说到了这个 我讨厌跟你击掌
While we're at it, I hate high-fiving you!
我知道
I know.
我们是睡在一起的成人
We're adults who are sleeping together,
不是宣誓入团的青少年
not teens pledging a frat.
哦 天哪 我很喜欢击掌
Oh, man, I really liked the high-five.
第二天早上 马修和莉莉起来发现了一个惊喜
The next morning, Marshall and Lily woke up to a surprise.
嘿 你们 你们在这里干嘛
Hey, what are... what are you guys doing here?
只是想确认一下钥匙好不好用
Just wanted to make sure this key worked.
我们很想你们
We missed you.
给准妈妈一个拥抱
Give mama a hug.
哦
Oh...
别看你的语音邮箱
Don't check your voicemail.
你可能有几条奇怪的留言
Y-You might have a couple weird ones.
听到这个了么
You hear this?!
这是我大步向前的声音
This is the sound of me moving on.
对啊 我是一个脱衣舞先生
Yeah, I'm a stripper.
好的 谁想要烤薄饼
Okay, who wants pancakes?
哪两个想要烤薄饼
Which two of you want pancakes?
我会再去做些的
I'll make more.
哦 好 很好 太棒了 因为我想要烤薄饼
Oh, good-good-good, 'cause I want pancakes.
这份给你
There you go.
谢谢 好的
Thank you, okay.
好好品尝吧
Enjoy them.
嘿 亲爱的 你看
Hey, honey, look,
很抱歉我之前行为很流氓
I'm sorry I was a jerk before.
我在早饭之后就走 好么
Okay? I'll leave right after breakfast.
我可以跟朋友挤一挤
I'll crash with some friends.
爸爸 你知道么
Dad, you know what?
你可以留在这里
You can stay.
哦 感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
我没有朋友
I got no friends.
我最多在这儿呆两周
I'll be here two weeks, tops.
他呆了不止两周
It wasn't two weeks.
我们五个人会一直过着
Would the five of us always live
几分钟内就可以到专座小聚的日子么
within a few minutes of that booth?
不 那就是生活 孩子们 但是我发现
No, that's life, kids, but here's what I discovered.
只要我们五个人在一起 坐的地方就叫专座
Our booth was wherever the five of us were together.
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
就是这样 寡妇罗德里格斯
That's right, Widow Rodriguez.
展开双臂
Stretch it.
抬起美腿
Work those gams.
哦 太对了
Ooh, yeah.
抓住左臂
Grab that left arm.
紧握胸脯
Clutch that chest.
快速倒下
Fall down really fast.
哦 天哪 谁打下急救电话
Oh, my God! Somebody call 911!